Frontend

Kutsenko Alexander

ngineus@gmail.com

mobile: +380 (67) 459-52-54, +380 (95) 820-92-85

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexander-kutsenko-571a4023/

https://www.facebook.com/ngineus

Applicant for the position: Junior Frontend Developer

Why Me

Why did I decide to go to Frontend from graphic design? Because it allows me to use my **previous experience (over 15 years in graphic design)** to **make good desing go smart.**

Additionally I continue my training – learning English.

It is important for me to boost my new knowledges on practice, so I will do my best to get success in Frontend.

Knowledge and technology

Frontend: HTML5/CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, SASS

Supporting technologies: Git, Grunt.

Graphic Design: Full stack of Adobe Creative Collection,

Quark XPress, Corel Draw

Supporting technologies: Extensis Pitstop, Kodak Preps, Heidelberg Package Designer and many other solutions. Knowledge of all the nuances in print production workflow from the formulation of the idea to preparing for production

Soft skills: Scrum, Time management

Foreign languages: English (B1+ Intermediate)

Experience

2016 - present time. Branding agency Polaris. Graphics designer

Responsibilities: adaptation of design for print and web production. Development of new advertising constructions. Prepress, product quality control. System administration.

2000 – 2016. BVI-Print, Printing house Head of the design department. Start from graphic designer.

Responsibilities: negotiations with customers, project management, team building of design department. For a long time also served as a system administrator. Web site support.

1998 - 2000. Excelsior Advertising agency. Designer

Responsibilities: prototyping and prepress for polygraphic products. Participated in all processes from design to installation. Later taught new employees.

Additional education

Frontend Developer (GoIT)
HTML/CSS (HTML Academy)

Personal information

Date of birth: 29 may Marital status: Married

Hobby: tourism, diving, photography and video shooting

Thank you for your attention to my CV!

Куценко Александр

ngineus@gmail.com

моб.: +380 (67) 459-52-54, +380 (95) 820-92-85

https://www.facebook.com/ngineus

Претендент на должность: Junior Frontend Developer

Почему я

Почему из графического дизайна я решил перейти именно во Frontend? Потому что он позволяет использовать мой опыт и **красивое делать умным и интерактивным.**

Хотя базовые знания мною уже изучены, я продолжаю свое обучение – хожу на курсы английского, записался на Angular.

Очень важно чтобы полученные мною новые знания на курсах Frontend были подкреплены решением практических задач, поэтому буду рад, если Вы положительно рассмотрите мою кандидатуру.

Знания и стек технологий

Frontend: HTML5/CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, SASS

Вспомогательные технологии: Git, Grunt.

Графический дизайн: Adobe (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign,

Acrobat), Quark XPress, Corel Draw

Вспомогательные технологии: Extensis Pitstop, Kodak Preps, Heidelberg Package Designer и еще много-много всего. Знание всех нюансов в прохождении заказа от постановки

задачи до подготовки макета к производству.

Soft skills: Scrum, Time management

Иностранные языки: English (B1+ Intermediate)

Опыт работы

2016 - по настоящее время.

Брендинговое агентство Polaris, Дизайнер

Обязанности: Адаптация дизайна для печати и web-дизайна, разработка новых рекламных конструкций, допечатная подготовка, контроль качества продукции. Системное администрирование.

2000 – 2016. "БВИ-Принт" типография, Руководитель отдела допечатной подготовки.

Новые обязанности: переговоры с клиентами, управление проектами, построение отдела дизайна. Обязанности: Дизайн, контроль качества, допечатная подготовка. Системное администрирование. Поддержка web-сайта.

Образование

Frontend Developer (GoIT)
HTML/CSS (HTML Academy)

О себе

Дата рождения: 29 мая **Семейное положение:** женат

Хобби: дайвинг, туризм, фотография и видеосъемка.

Спасибо за внимание к моему резюме!